Salvatore, Nick, Research files /4249
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Singing in a Strange Land Research Materials. Box C. (Box 16)
  - Drum/Rev. Workers (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Housing 1945-60 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Post 1975-76 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Black Culture and Religion: Reports (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Race/Class in Neighborhoods (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Black Political and Cultural Activism (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Black Story-telling/Oral History (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - America and Religion (Focus on African-Americas) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "Chicago's History" Fall 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Neighborhood Maps (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - "How Sweet the Sound" (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Sand Against the Wind" (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Religious - Misc. (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Singing in a Strange Land 3 Drafts and C. L. Franklin sermons.. (Box 17)
  - Chapter 1: A Deep Longing (8/24/00 - rewritten 9/3/00) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 2: Attempting His Imagination (3/9/01) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 3: Moving on Up (2/2/02) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 4: The Eagle Stirs (5/31/02) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 5: Hastings Street (11/1/02) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 6: Thoughts of Liberation (1/24/03) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 7: Just a Man (3/10/03) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 8 (8/11/03) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 9: A Rising Wind (9/23/03) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 10: Preaching no More (11/8/03) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Epilogue (11/12/03) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 1: "A Deep Longing" re-written 5/14/03 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 2: "Attempting His Imagination" Re-written 5/21/03 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 3: "Moving on Up" 5/30/03 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 4: "The Eagle Stirreth" 6/4/03 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 5: "Hastings Street" 6/11/03 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 6; "Thoughts of Liberation" 6/20/03 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 7: "Just a Man" 6/26/03 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 1: A Deep Longing (11/12/03) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 2: Attempting His Imagination (11/13/03) (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 3: Moving on Up (11/18/03) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 4: The Eagle Stirreth (11/19/03) (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 5: Hastings Street (11/21/03) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 6: Thoughts of Liberation (11/23/03) (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 7: Just a Man (11/24/03) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 8: Emmett Till (12/03/03) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 9: A Rising Wind (12/06/03) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 10: Now He is Down (12/10/03) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Epilogue (12/10/03) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Acknowledgements (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Bibliography as of 12/8/03 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - 1 CLF, "The Twenty-Third Psalm," early 1950s (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 2. CLF, "The Eagle Stirreth Her Nest" (1953) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - 2b. "The Eagle Stirreth in Her Nest" (1963) (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - 3. "The Prodigal Son" (1954) (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - 4. "Pressing On" (1955) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - 5. "Following Jesus" (1955) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - 6. "The Rich Young Ruler" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - 7. "How Long Halt Ye Between Two Opinions?" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - 8. "Dry Bones in the Valley" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - 9. "Without a Song" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 10. "Jacob Wrestling the Angel" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - 11. "The Story of Job" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - 12. "The Inner Conflict" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - 13. "Moses at the Red Sea" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - 14. "What Must I do to be Saved?" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - 15. "Ye Must be Born Again" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - 16. "The Barren Fig Tree" (1955) (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - 17. "Counting the Cost" (1955/56) (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - 18. "Lo, I am With You Always" (1/1/1956) (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - 19. "Behold, I Send you Like Sheep into a Pack of Wolves" (5/5/1978) (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - 20. "Moses Sends Twelve Spies" (Jan. 1956) (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - 21. "Did Not Our Hearts Burn While he Talked by the Wayside?" (April 1956) (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - 22. "Nothing Shall Separate Me from the Love of God" (mid-1950s) (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - 23. "Give me This Mountain" (V1= late 1950s; V2=1963) (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - 24. "What Think Ye of Jesus?" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - 25. "The King of the Jews" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - 26. "Two Fishes and Five Loaves of Bread" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - 27. "The Man at the Pool (1950s)" and "Jesus at Bethesda (10/16/1977)" (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - 28. "The Fiery Furnace" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - 29. "Silver and Gold I Have None" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - 30. "Ye are the Salt of Earth" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - 31. "Except I Shall See in his Hands" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - 32. "All Things Work Together for Good to Them That Love God" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - 33. "Why are Ye So Afraid, O Ye of Little Faith?" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - 34. "Hannah, the Ideal Mother" (late 1950s) (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - 35. "The Eternity of the Church" (pre-1963, then 10/2/1977) (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - 36. "The Foolish and the Wise Builders" (pre-1963) (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - 37. "Nehemiah and the Great Work" (pre-1963) (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - 38. "The Devil Tempts Jesus (pre-1963)" and "Satan Goes to Prayer Meeting (1975)" (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - 39. "Study to Show Thyself to God" (pre-1963) (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - 40. "The Rich Man and the Beggar (pre-1963)" and "Dives, Lazarus and the Dogs (10/2/1977)" (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - 41. "What of the Night" (1956-63) (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - 42. "Fret Not Thyself" (pre-1963) (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - 43. "hose the Prophet and Gomer the Prostitute" (pre-1963) (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - 44. "The King, Lord of Hosts" (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - 45. "This is my Beloved Son (pre-1964)" and "A Mountain-Top Vision (10/30/1977)" (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - 46. "The Project of Making Man" (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - 47. "Fishermen, Drop your Nets (pre-1964)" and "Meeting Jesus in the Dawn (4/30/1978)" (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - 48."Wheel in the Middle of a Wheel" (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - 49. "A Wild Man Meets Jesus" (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - 50. "The Challenge of Christmas" (1962) (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - 51. Paul's Hymn of Love (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - 52. The 100th Psalm (The Lord is Good) (pre-1964) (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - 53. John's Vision of a New Heaven (pre-1965) (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - 54. Paul's Meditation on Immortality (pre-1965) (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - 55. Jesus Meets the Woman at the Well (pre-1965) (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - 56. And He Went a Little Farther (1965) (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - 57. There's Danger in a Crowd (1967) (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - 58. Why Have the Mighty Fallen So? (1968) (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - 59. My Kingdom is Not of This World (1969) (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - 60. The Preacher Who Got Drunk (1969) (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - 61. Man on the Moon (1969) (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - 62. I Heard it Through the Grapevine (1969) (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - 63. The Meaning of Black Power (1969) (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - 64. Come Unto Me, Lazarus (1960s) (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - 65. The Golden Calf (1971) (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - 66. Let Your Hair Down (1971) (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - 67. The Lord's Prayer (1972) (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - 68. The Greatest Love Story (1973) (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - 69. A Bigot Meets Jesus (1973) (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - 70. What is Your Life (1975) (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - 71. Refusal to the Banquet of God (10/16/1977) (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - 72. The Man Who Went to Heaven Without Dying (11/7/1977) (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - 73. Fishermen or Shepherds? (5/7/1978) (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - 74. A Mother at the Cross (5/14/1978) (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - 75. Finding Oneself in a Cave (5/7/1978) (Box 17, Folder 107)
- Singing in a Strange Land Subject Index Cards. Box 1 of 3. (Box 18)
  - Mississippi 1915 Part 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mississippi 1915 Part 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mississippi 1915 Part 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Memphis 1938/9 Part 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Memphis 1938/9 Part 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Detroit Part 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Detroit Part 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Detroit Part 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Singing in a Strange Land Subject Index Cards. Box 2 of 3. (Box 19)
  - History: Pre-1946 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1946-57 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1957-67 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1957-67 Part 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1967-84 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Family (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lifestyle (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Death/Memorials (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - History (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Administration of NBB (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Departments (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Congregation (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Singing in a Strange Land Subject Index Cards. Box 3 of 3. (Box 20)
  - Personal Testimony and Politics (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NBC Part 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - NBC Part 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sermons Part 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sermons Part 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sermons Part 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Departments/Officers (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Tenure Fight/Split (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Politics/Social Issues (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Statistics (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Race (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Singing in a Strange Land Title Index Cards. (Box 21)
  - Add to Bibliography: Books and Articles Part 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Add to Bibliography: Books and Articles Part 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Add to Bibliography: Books and Articles Part 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Add to Bibliography: Discography (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Add to Bibliography: Government Documents (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Add to Bibliography: Interviews by NS (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Add to Bibliography: Interviews by Others (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Add to Bibliography: Proceedings (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Add to Bibliography: Manuscripts (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Add to Bibliography: Newspapers and Magazines (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Add to Bibliography: Sermons (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Add to Bibliography: Theses and Dissertations (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Add to Bibliography: Acknowledgements (Box 21, Folder 13)